Finding Aid for the Martin Perlich Interviews PASC-M.0341
UCLA Library Special Collections
Martin Perlich interviews
1965-2008
UCLA Library Special Collections
Perlich, Martin
PASC-M.0341
6.0 linear feet (12 boxes)
The collection predominantly consists of Martin Perlich's radio and video interviews with musicians, actors and comedians. Also included in the collection are papers pertaining to Perlich's life and career as a writer, producer and broadcaster.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
COLLECTION CONTAINS DIGITAL MATERIALS: Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To access digital materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9966266003606533
Biographical Note
Writer, Producer and distinguished broadcaster, Martin Perlich, has hosted and produced the interview series, ARF!! (Arts & Roots Forum) which aired daily on Los Angeles public radio and featured major cultural figures, from Stacy Keach to Terry Riley to Sandra Tsing Loh to avant-garde playwright Murray Mednic, as well as dozens of arts figures: writers, directors, choreographers and musical figures from Jazz, Wolrd music and classical music.
From 2000-8 Perlich served as Program Director responsible for all programming of the Los Angeles public radio station, KCSN. In addition, he hosted an acclaimed daily classical and New Music show. His historic interview show, "Martin Perlich Interviews" featuring Leonard Bernstin, Frank Zappa, Pierre Boulz and hundreds more, was syndicated nationally by WCLV/Seaway productions.
Perlich's early work was in musicology. After studying with American composer, Douglas Moore at Columbia University, he was for seven years, Intermission Host of the internationally syndicated Cleveland Orchestra radio broadcasts.
His award-winning Martin Perlich Interviews was syndicated nationally and aired locally on public radio station, KCSN, where he was Program Director of, as well as classical Host and interviewer.
In the 1960s Perlich was a pioneer in "experimental radio" beginning in 1972 with KMET in Los Angeles. In 1975, Perlich became Creative Consultant of NBC "The Midnight Special." In the 1980s he developed and produced dramatic and musical programming at PBS's KCET in Los Angeles and WNET in New York, and a feature film, "The Trial of Ramona Africa" with Whoopie Goldberg for American Playhouse and Channel 4 in London.
Scope and Content
The collection predominantly consists of Martin Perlich's radio interviews with musicians, actors and comedians. Also included in the collection are papers pertaining to Perlich's life and career as a writer, producer and broadcaster.
The collection is in the midst of being processed and the finding aid will be updated periodically.
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1. Interviews
Online Items Available
Portions of this collection have been digitized and are available online: Martin Perlich Interviews (343 items).
Interviews.; Entertainers -- Interviews.
- Interviews, Series 1.
  - Best of Martin Perlich Interviews, 2003; compact disc (Box 8)
    Scope and Contents note
    John Adams -- Mitsuko Uchida -- Esa Pekka Salonen -- Joshua Bell -- Kathleen Battle -- Isaac Stern.
  - Martin Perlich Interview Archives, compact disc (Box 8)
    Kronos Quartet: David Harrington -- Hillary Hahn -- Joshua Bell -- Essa-Pekka Salonen.
  - Martin Perlich Interview Archives, compact disc (Box 8)
    Ollie Mustonen -- Andre Watts -- Evelyn Glennie.
  - Martin Perlich Interview Archives, 2002 November 14; compact disc (Box 8)
    John Mauceri -- Upcut -- Pavo Jarvi.
  - Martin Perlich Interview Archives, compact disc (Box 8)
    R. Gilfry -- G. Mester -- Lang Lang -- L. Nimoy -- F. Fennel.
  - Martin Perlich Interview Archive, compact disc (Box 9)
    Kahane -- Jarvi -- Graham -- Gilfry.
  - Martin Perlich Interview Archives, compact disc (Box 9)
    James Conlon -- Dohnanyi.
  - Martin Perlich Interview Archives, compact disc (Box 9)
    Vera Zorina -- Alice Chalifoux -- Maurine Forrester -- James Oliver Buswell IV.
  - Martin Perlich Interview Archives, compact disc (Box 9)
    Edith Peinenmen -- Pierre Bernac -- Tamas Vasary -- Lorin Hollander.
  - Martin Perlich Interview Archives, compact disc (Box 9)
    Peter Frankl -- Martyn Green -- Louis Lane -- Goddard Lieberson.
  - Martin Perlich Interview Archives, compact disc (Box 9)
    Alfred Brendel -- Evelyn Glennie -- Kronos Quartet -- Hillary Hahn.
  - Accardo, Salvatore, 2003 November 13; minidisc (Box 4)
    Duration: 28:04
    General note
    Compact disc copy in box 9.
    Note
    Subject is a violinist.
  - Ackerman, Hal, 2008 April 24; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "Testosterone."
    The subject is the co-chair of the screenwriting program at the UCLA School of Theater, Film and Television. He is a playwright and author.
  - Acuna, Alex, 2007 June 11; compact disc (Box 8)
    The subject is a percussionist.
  - Adams, John, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
    master tape
    The subject is a composer.
    Other Copies
    Digital transfer in DLP.
  - Adams, John, 2001 February 1; compact disc (Box 8)
    Minidisc copy in box 4.
  - Adams, John, 2001 March 27; compact disc (Box 8)
  - Adams, John, 2001 November 14; minidisc (Box 4)
    Recorded at Zipper Hall. Compact disc copy in box 9.
  - Adams, John, 2001 January 26; DAT (Box 6)
  - Adams, John, 1997; compact disc (Box 9)
    On item, "Century Rolls."
  - Adams, John, 1989 February 11; audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Ahn Trio, 2007 May 9; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 30:29.
    The Ahn Trio is a piano trio made up of sisters, Angella, Lucia, and Maria Ahn.
  - Aks, David, 2008 January 3; compact disc (Box 7)
    With Ann Baltz.
    The subject is a cellist.
  - Amram, David, 2003 July 31; DAT (Box 8)
    The subject is a composer and conductor.
  - Anker, Daniel, 2006 March 22; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Anonymous 4, 2006 September 26; compact disc (Box 5)
    Marsha Genensky and Susan Hellauer.
  - Anonymous 4, 2006 October 1; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 29:51.
  - The Arizona Project: Michael F. Wendland, audio cassette (Box 6)
    Scope and Contents
    Book on organized crime in Arizona
  - Arpino, Gerald, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
    The subject is a dancer,choreographer and co-founder of the Joffrey Ballet.
  - Arpino, Gerald, 1990 March 23; audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Assad, Sergio, 2003 October 2; DAT (Box 6)
    The subject is a guitarist and composer.
  - Attiyeh, Robert, streaming video
    The subject is President of Yarlung Records and founder of nonprofit organization Yarlung Artitst.
  - Auger, Arleen, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
    The subject is a soprano.
  - Averbach, Lera, 2005 July 14; compact disc (Box 5)
    The subject is a writer, composer, pianist.
  - Averbach, Lera, 2004 February 19; DAT (Box 6)
  - Avery, James, 2005 June 2; compact disc (Box 7)
    The subject is an actor.
  - Avery, James, 2005 June 20; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 29:30.
  - Ax, Emanuel, 1989 January 4; audio cassette (Box 12)
    Duration: 27:52
    The subject is an American pianist.
  - Ax, Emanuel, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - Barbosa-Lima, Carlos, 2002 March 13; DAT (Box 6)
    The subject is a guitarist.
  - Bartoli, Cecilia, 2005 October 6; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 30:03.
    The subject is a mezzo-soprano.
  - Batalla, Perla, 2007 February 13; compact disc (Box 5)
    The subject is a Mexican-American singer-songwriter.
  - Battle, Kathleen, 1989 March 3; compact disc (Box 7)
    Duration: 29:59.
    2 discs. Audio cassette copy in box 12. Compact disc copy on one disc in box 9.
    The subject is an American lyric soprano.
  - Battle, Kathleen, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - Beal, Jeff, 2006 December 5; compact disc (Box 5)
    Duration: 30:23.
    On disc, "Molly Barnes." Compact disc copy in box 9.
  - Beasley, Karen, 1990 August 13; audio cassette (Box 6)
    Also includes: Karan Armstrong, soprano, and Gotz Friederich.
    On item,"Fidelio."
  - Begley, Ed Jr., 2003 May 2; DAT (Box 6)
    The subject is an actor and environmental activist
  - Bell, Joshua, 2001 May 25; minidisc (Box 4)
    On item, "Bernstein." Duration: 33:15.
    Subject is a violinist
  - Bell, Joshua, 2001 January 18; DAT (Box 6)
  - Bell, Joshua, 2006 October 29; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Bell, Joshua, 2006 November 20; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 30:10.
  - Bemel, Dereck, 2007 January 19; compact disc (Box 8)
  - Bermel, Derek, streaming video
    Subject is a composer, clarinettist and conductor.
  - Bernstein, Leonard, audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Bicket, Harry, 2005 November 3; compact disc (Box 8)
  - Biller, Anna, 2007 March 6; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "Viva."
  - Bilson, Malcolm, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Bilson, Malcolm, 1990 February 9; audio cassette (Box 11)
  - Bishop, Stephen, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3)
  - Bishop, Steven, 1990; 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Biss, Jonathan, 2007 July 18; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Black, Karen, 2007 May 19; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 29:28.
  - Bland, Ed, 2004 April 9; DAT (Box 6)
  - Blumenstock, Elizabeth, 2007 November 7; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Bonoff, Karla, audio cassette (Box 10)
  - Boulez, Pierre, 1989 May 15; audio cassette (Box 11)
  - Brendel, Alfred, 2002 April 4; minidisc (Box 4)
    Duration: 51:09
  - Brendel, Alfred, 2004 April 3; compact disc (Box 7)
    Minidisc copy in box 9.
  - Brenneman, Amy, 2006 October 4; compact disc (Box 5)
    Subject is an actress, writer and producer
  - Brevoort, Deborah, 2007 February 29; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Bridel, David, 2008 May 27; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "I Gelosi."
  - Bridel, David, 2008 May 29; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Bronfman, Yefim, 1990 July 28; audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Brown, Iona, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Brown, Iona, 1991 April 22; audio cassette (Box 6)
  - Brown, Iona, 1990 March 3; audio cassette (Box 11)
    Duration: 32:10
    master tape. Compact disc copy in box 9.
  - Brown, Oscar Jr., 2000 November 17; DAT (Box 6)
  - Brown, Oscar Jr., 2001 March 31; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 30:16
  - Browne, Jackson, 1977 August 3; compact disc (Box 7)
    2 discs. Also on 2 cassettes (one missing) in box 12.
    subject is a singer-songwriter
  - Brueggen, Franz, 1989 April 27; audio cassette (Box 12)
    Also with Anner Bylsma
  - Bryant, Clora, 2007 March 22; compact disc (Box 5)
    Subject is a jazz trumpeter.
  - Bryant, Clora, 2007 May 7; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Bryars, Gavin, 2004 March 16; DAT (Box 6)
  - Budd, Harold, 2003 October 6; DAT (Box 6)
  - Burdon, Eric, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
    Electric Tongue
  - Bylsma, Anner, 1989 April 27; compact disc (Box 7)
    Duration: 56:56.
  - Bylsma, Anner, 1989 April 27; compact disc (Box 7)
    2 discs.
  - Bylsma, Anner, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3)
  - Calder Quartet, 2006 October 18; compact disc (Box 7)
    Includes interviews with Andrew Bulbrook and Benjamin Jacobson.
  - Camblin, Zina, 2008 June 5; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Camplin, Zina, 2008 June 3; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "And Her Hair Went With Her."
  - Carlson, Mark, 2006 May 22; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Carradine, Keith, 1978 April 5; audio cassette (Box 10)
  - Carrington, Simon, 1990 July 11; audio cassette (Box 6)
    Of the King's Singers.
  - Carter, Elliott, streaming video
  - Cartwright, Nancy, 2007 September 21; compact disc (Box 5)
    Voice of Bart Simpson.
  - Castro, Cesar, 2007 October 19; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Catan, Daniel, streaming video
  - Catan, Daniel, 2004 January 29; DAT (Box 6)
  - Chandler, Charlotte, audio cassette (Box 4)
    On item, "Groucho."
  - Chang, Sarah, 2001 May 9; minidisc (Box 4)
    Duration: 33:45
  - Chang, Sarah, 2001 December 25; DAT (Box 6)
  - Chang, Sarah, 2002 April 23; DAT (Box 8)
  - Charlton, Frederick, 2005 Feburary 1; DAT (Box 6)
  - Cheng, Gloria, streaming video
    Subject is a pianist and UCLA faculty member.
  - Cheng, Gloria, 2005 October 12; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Chernov, Vladimir, 2007 April 30; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Childs, Billy, 2004 February 19; DAT (Box 6)
  - Childs, Billy, 2005 February 7; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 28:46
  - Clarke, Stanley, 1979 March 21; audio cassette (Box 4)
  - Clarke, Stanley, 1971 March 29; compact disc (Box 8)
    Disc 1 of 2. Disc 2 missing.
  - Cleveland Orchestra Interviews, compact disc (Box 9)
    Judith Raskin -- Julian Bream -- Pierre Fournier -- Itzhak Perlman -- Emil Gilels.
  - Cleveland Orchestra Interviews, compact disc (Box 9)
    Fernando Valenti -- Darius Milhaud -- Lucas Foss -- Casadesus Family.
  - Cleveland Orchestra Interviews, compact disc (Box 9)
    Romero Family -- Robert Shaw -- Aurthur Fiedler.
  - Cohen, Jeremy, 2006 July 13; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Collette, Buddy, 2008 June 5; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Collette, Buddy, 2008 June 19; compact disc (Box 7)
    With Richard Simon.
  - Collins, Judy, 1979 March 16; audio cassette (Box 6)
    Recorded at the Beverly Hills Hotel.
    Audio cassette is damaged.
  - Collins, Judy, 1979 March 16; audio cassette (Box 10)
  - Conlon, James, streaming video
  - Conlon, James, 2002 April 23; minidisc (Box 4)
    Duration: 40:57.
  - Corigliano, John, 2004 May 7; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Costa, Pedro, 2007 September 20; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Costa, Pedro, 2007 September 25; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 29:45
  - Country Joe, audio cassette (Box 10)
    Subject is a musician and lead singer for the psychedelic rock group, Country Joe and the Fish.
  - Cypress String Quartet, 2007 June 20; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Daugherty, Michael, 2004 December 11; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Daugherty, Michael, 2004 December 11; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Daversa, John, 2008 January 24; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Daviau, Allen, 2007 March 9; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Davidson, 1990 May 1; audio cassette (Box 12)
    On item, "re-edited."
  - Davies, Ray, 1978 June 25; compact disc (Box 8)
    Of The Kinks.
    3 discs. Audio cassette copy (2 cassettes) in box 10.
  - Davis, Don, streaming video
  - Davis, Don, 2005 October 28; compact disc (Box 8)
  - Davis, Don, 2006 June 29; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 30:11.
  - Davis, Heidi Helen, 2007 July 6; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "Blithe Spirit."
  - De Lancie, John, 2004 February 5; DAT (Box 6)
  - de Wart, Edo, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - de Wart, Edo, audio cassette (Box 4)
  - de Wart, Ed, 1989; compact disc (Box 7)
  - del Monte, Adam, 2004 January 19; DAT (Box 8)
  - Denali Quartet, 2005 January 10; DAT (Box 8)
  - Devo (Musical Group), 1979 May 2; audio cassette (Box 10)
  - Diaz, Justino, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3)
  - Diaz, Justino, 1989 Auguts 23; audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Dibie, George Spiro, 2007 March 9; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Dichter, Misha and Sipa, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Dichter, Misha and Sipa, 1990 February 20; audio cassette (Box 6)
  - DiMeola, Al, 1978 May 26; audio cassette (Box 10)
  - Dixie Dregs: Steve Morse, 1979 July 26; audio cassette (Box 4)
    Recorded at the Tropicana Hotel, Los Angeles.
  - Dohnanyi, Christoph von, 1989 April 17; compact disc (Box 7)
    Duration: 46:27.
    2 discs. Copy on one disc in box 9.
    Subject is a German composer.
  - Dohnanyi, Christoph von, 1989 April 7; audio cassette (Box 11)
  - Domingo, Placido, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
    With Julia Migenens
  - Donohoe, Peter, 1988 November 4; audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Douglas, Barry, 1989 March 6; audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Dowling, Vincent, 2007 June 13; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Dowling, Vincent, 2007 February 16; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Dowling, Vincent, 2007 October 24; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Dowling, Vincent, 2007 October 25; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 25:13
  - Dowling, Vincent, 2007 June 26; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Downes, Lara, 2003 March 14; DAT (Box 8)
  - Drane, Evan, 2008 July 10; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Drane, Evan, 2008 July 9; compact disc (Box 5)
    On Disc, "Spring Awards."
  - Drayton, Leslie, 2006 June 2; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Druckman, Jacob, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Du Bois, Alexandra, streaming video
  - Dunleavy, Mary, 2008 February 11; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Edwards, Betty, 1979 September 25; audio cassette (Box 10)
    Author of "Drawing on the Right Side of the Brain."
  - Ehnes, James, 2006 July 11; compact disc (Box 8)
  - Eighth Blackbird, streaming video
  - Elinaudi, Ludovico, streaming video
  - Elliott, Jeff and Julia Rodriguez, 2008 March 10; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "A Noise Within."
  - Evans, Bill, 1978 April 5; compact disc (Box 7)
    2 discs. Also on 2 audio cassettes in box 11.
  - Farber, Stephen, 2006 May 24; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Farley, Keythe, 2007 July 10; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "Gulliver's Travels."
  - Fejer, Andras, 2003 October 20; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Feltsman, Vladimir, 1990 May 15; compact disc (Box 7)
    Audio cassette copy in box 12.
    Subject is a Russian-American pianist
  - Feltsman, Vladimir, 1990; 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Fialka, Gerry, 2004 August 25; DAT (Box 8)
  - Finney, Shirley Jo, 2007 November 15; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Fischer, Ivan, 2003 April 17; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Fleisher, Leon, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Fowley, Kim, 1977 October 31; audio cassette (Box 4)
    On Steven T. recording
  - Fowley, Kim, audio cassette (Box 4)
  - Fox, Brendon, 2006 January 27; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Fox, Brendon, 2007 April 12; compact disc (Box 7)
    With Kurtwood Smith.
  - Frank, Claude, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3)
  - Fried, Miriam, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - Furhy, Richie, 1978 May 17; audio cassette (Box 4)
  - Gallagher, Michael, 2006 April 5; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Garcetti, Gil, 2008 September 27; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Gardenhire, Robin, 2006 October 5; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Gatti, Daniele, 2004 February 4; minidisc (Box 4)
    Duration: 26:40
  - Geer, Ellen, 2005 July 7; compact disc (Box 7)
    Subject is an actress, professor and theater director.
  - Geer, Ellen, 2008 July 3; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Geer, Ellen, 2006 June 8; compact disc (Box 7)
    With Abby Craden.
  - Geer, Ellen, 2008 June 26; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Geer, Ellen, 2006 May 31; compact disc (Box 7)
    On disc, "Antony and Cleopatra."
  - Gershon, Grant, streaming video
  - Gershon, Grant, 2004 January 20; DAT (Box 6)
  - Gershon, Grant, 2005 September 25; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 29:54
  - Gershon, Grant, 2006 September 25; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Gershon, Grant, 2007 January 23; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Gershon, Grant, 2006 October 12; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Gershon, Grant, 2007 October 8; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Gibson, Ralph, 2006 October 5; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Gilbert, Taylor, 2007 October 2; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Gioia, Dana, streaming video
  - Glass, Phillip, 1978 November 16; compact disc (Box 7)
    Master tape on audio cassette in box 11.
  - Glass, Phillip, 1978 November 6; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Glass, Philip, 1983 May; audio cassette (Box 10)
    With Godfrey Reggio.
    On container, "Koyaanisqotsi."
  - Glennie, Evelyn, 2002 March 20; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Glennie, Evelyn, 2002 March 28; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Global Village, 2006 May 25; compact disc (Box 8)
  - Global Village, 2006 June 1; compact disc (Box 8)
  - Goffman, Mark, 2006 June 1; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "Me Too."
  - Goldwyn, Samuel Jr., 1989 March 31; audio cassette (Box 4)
  - Golijov, Osvaldo, 2004 February 27; minidisc (Box 4)
  - Gondek, Juliana, 2004 May 6; DAT (Box 6)
  - Gonzalez, Nicholas, 2006 January 16; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "Dialects of the Heart."
  - Goode, Michael, 2006 April 12; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Goode, Michael, 2006 May 11; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Gordon, Dexter, 1979 June 14; audio cassette (Box 4)
    Recorded at the Continental Hyatt House.
    Compact disc copy (2 discs) in box 7.
  - Gordon, Michael, 2008 January 8; compact disc (Box 8)
    With Bill Morrison.
  - Graham, Susan, 2002 September 10; minidisc (Box 4)
    Duration: 26:24.
  - Griggs, Whitney, 2006 May 9; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Grimaud, Helene, 2006 September 20; compact disc (Box 7)
    On disc, "Original iterview with mistakes."
    Edited version on compact disc in box 9.
  - Gross, Allen, 2006 March 21; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Guarneri Quartet, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3)
    With Arnold Steinhardt
  - Guinand, Maria, streaming video
  - Gurwitch, Annabelle, 2006 April 27; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Hahn, Hilary, 2002 May 1; minidisc (Box 4)
    Duration:53:58
  - Haimovitz, Matt, streaming video
  - Haimovitz, Matt, DAT (Box 6)
  - Haimovitz, Matt, 2006 January 17; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Haimovitz, Matt, 2006 January 26; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Hampson, Thomas, 1990 April 22; audio cassette (Box 12)
    Duration: 37:15
  - Hampson, Thomas, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - Han, Wu, 2007 November 12; compact disc (Box 8)
  - Han, Zhiming, 2006 December 19; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Harrell, Lynne, 1990; 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Harrell, Lynn, 1990 July 13; audio cassette (Box 11)
  - Harrington, David, streaming video
  - Harrison, Michael, 2005 October 27; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Hartley, Mariette, 2008 April 21; compact disc (Box 5)
    With husband, Jerry Sroka.
  - Hartley, Mariette, 2006 January 20; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Hartley, Mariette, 2006 February 1; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 29:36.
  - Heasley, Tom, streaming video
  - Heasley, Tom, 2005 November 1; compact disc (Box 8)
  - Heggie, Jake, 2008 May 29; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Heggie, Jake, 2008 June 12; compact disc (Box 9)
  - Helnwein, Mercedes, 2008 March 6; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Hicks, Dan, 1979 June 2; audio cassette (Box 10)
    Recorded at the Tropicana.
  - Hirsch, Vicki, 2007 June 18; compact disc (Box 5)
    On disc, "Song fest."
  - Hoenig, Michael, 1978 February 23; audio cassette (Box 12)
    On 2 audio cassettes.
  - Hogwood, Christopher, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Hogwood, Christopher, 1988 December 7; audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Holder, Kate, 2007 February 7; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Hung, Gao, 2004 January 15; DAT (Box 8)
  - Hope, Daniel, 2006 February 10; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Horne, Marilyn, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 2)
  - Horne, Marilyn, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3)
  - Horne, Marilyn, 1990; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 14:01
  - Horne, Marilyn, 1990 September 27; audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Hosken, Dan, 2007 March 23; compact disc (Box 5)
    With Young Riddle.
  - Hough, Stephen, 10" open reel audio tape (Box 1)
  - Hough, Stephen, 1989 February 11; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 26:37.
  - Hough, Stephen, audio cassette (Box 12)
  - Huebner, Eric, 2007 November 30; compact disc (Box 8)
    with Daniel Rothman.
  - Huggett, Monica, 2001 October 18; DAT (Box 8)
  - Hurley, Susan, 2006 February 10; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Iglesias, Alberto, 2007 December 7; compact disc (Box 8)
  - Iglesias, Alberto, 2007 December 13; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 29:50.
  - Isham, Mark, 2007 November 14; compact disc (Box 5)
  - Isham, Mark, 2005 June 10; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Isham, Mark, 2005 June 20; compact disc (Box 9)
    Duration: 29:53.
  - Iyengar, Malathi, 2004 September 9; DAT (Box 8)
  - Jacaranda, streaming video
  - Jacobson, James, 2006 January 24; compact disc (Box 7)
  - Jarvi, Neeme, 1989 May 4; audio cassette (Box 11)
    Duration: 29:57
  - Jarvi, Paavo, 2002 July 8; minidisc (Box 4)
    Duration: 44:55.